[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "How do you feel about that analogy?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "that", "analogy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "I have no idea how to respond to that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "no", "idea", "how", "to", "respond", "to", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "Do you genuinely believe you could become the nominee?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "genuinely", "believe", "you", "could", "become", "the", "nominee", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "NN", "NN", "NN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "I suppose what I would say to you about is it can be a stick to beat you with in the sense that if you never change your mind about anything, is that in itself healthy?", "question_tokens": ["I", "suppose", "what", "I", "would", "say", "to", "you", "about", "is", "it", "can", "be", "a", "stick", "to", "beat", "you", "with", "in", "the", "sense", "that", "if", "you", "never", "change", "your", "mind", "about", "anything", ",", "is", "that", "in", "itself", "healthy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "VBZ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "Time and history help change your views.", "answer_tokens": ["Time", "and", "history", "help", "change", "your", "views", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "Do you have a regime on the campaign?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "a", "regime", "on", "the", "campaign", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "Yes, and it gets interrupted sometimes in the campaign.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "and", "it", "gets", "interrupted", "sometimes", "in", "the", "campaign", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 81, "question": "So, what do you do exercise-wise when you have time?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "what", "do", "you", "do", "exercise-wise", "when", "you", "have", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "OK.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 95, "question": "I mean, do you have a strict regime on that?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "do", "you", "have", "a", "strict", "regime", "on", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 96, "answer": "Not overly strict.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "overly", "strict", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 124, "question": "And if the answer is no, is that one of the fundamental problems that the work ethic has evolved over the years?", "question_tokens": ["And", "if", "the", "answer", "is", "no", ",", "is", "that", "one", "of", "the", "fundamental", "problems", "that", "the", "work", "ethic", "has", "evolved", "over", "the", "years", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 125, "answer": "I think that's a big issue.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "'s", "a", "big", "issue", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "Was that basically how you feel?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "that", "basically", "how", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "Yes, but it's a lot more compassionate than the way, you know, it might sound.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "but", "it", "'s", "a", "lot", "more", "compassionate", "than", "the", "way", ",", "you", "know", ",", "it", "might", "sound", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "Is it, though?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", ",", "though", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", ",", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "Yes, really because if you see the extent of total socialism, it's not very compassionate.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "really", "because", "if", "you", "see", "the", "extent", "of", "total", "socialism", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "very", "compassionate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 153, "question": "What is wrong with that as a principle, an ambition to aspire to?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "wrong", "with", "that", "as", "a", "principle", ",", "an", "ambition", "to", "aspire", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 154, "answer": "Well, I think the basic principle is wrong in that you don't have a right to somebody else's life or money.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "the", "basic", "principle", "is", "wrong", "in", "that", "you", "do", "n't", "have", "a", "right", "to", "somebody", "else", "'s", "life", "or", "money", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 165, "question": "What do they do?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "they", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "Well --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "Under your presidency, what would they do to get health care?", "question_tokens": ["Under", "your", "presidency", ",", "what", "would", "they", "do", "to", "get", "health", "care", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "You have to understand the difference between interventionist economy and a socialist economy.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "have", "to", "understand", "the", "difference", "between", "interventionist", "economy", "and", "a", "socialist", "economy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 193, "question": "Or how would you summarize your feelings?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "how", "would", "you", "summarize", "your", "feelings", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 194, "answer": "I wouldn't give him too much credit.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "n't", "give", "him", "too", "much", "credit", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 208, "question": "Can I answer that?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "I", "answer", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 209, "answer": "Well, let me read you this quote.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "let", "me", "read", "you", "this", "quote", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 215, "question": "Isn't it a better thing that the more credible position for Republicans to say, is to say, I am encouraged by this, but he should have gone further?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "it", "a", "better", "thing", "that", "the", "more", "credible", "position", "for", "Republicans", "to", "say", ",", "is", "to", "say", ",", "I", "am", "encouraged", "by", "this", ",", "but", "he", "should", "have", "gone", "further", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNPS", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 216, "answer": "To me, it's more important to admit the truth.", "answer_tokens": ["To", "me", ",", "it", "'s", "more", "important", "to", "admit", "the", "truth", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "And it just sounded awful, that, didn't it, for somebody aiming to be president to talk about the poor in that way?", "question_tokens": ["And", "it", "just", "sounded", "awful", ",", "that", ",", "did", "n't", "it", ",", "for", "somebody", "aiming", "to", "be", "president", "to", "talk", "about", "the", "poor", "in", "that", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "IN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "CD", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "CC", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBZ", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBN", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "Would they be yours?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "they", "be", "yours", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "If that's your number one priority, if you listen to what I have been talking about and understood free market economics, you would say the most important thing you can do is give them a sound currency, limited government, free markets, contract rights.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "that", "'s", "your", "number", "one", "priority", ",", "if", "you", "listen", "to", "what", "I", "have", "been", "talking", "about", "and", "understood", "free", "market", "economics", ",", "you", "would", "say", "the", "most", "important", "thing", "you", "can", "do", "is", "give", "them", "a", "sound", "currency", ",", "limited", "government", ",", "free", "markets", ",", "contract", "rights", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 268, "question": "What is wrong with that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "wrong", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 269, "answer": "Well, let him pay.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "let", "him", "pay", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 271, "question": "What is wrong with having a tax system which just taxes people like him more?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "wrong", "with", "having", "a", "tax", "system", "which", "just", "taxes", "people", "like", "him", "more", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "RB", "VBZ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "It destroys the economy if you just --", "answer_tokens": ["It", "destroys", "the", "economy", "if", "you", "just", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "-- you got to have a president who prioritizes the poor, haven't you?", "question_tokens": ["--", "you", "got", "to", "have", "a", "president", "who", "prioritizes", "the", "poor", ",", "have", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "OK.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 324, "question": "Even if it works?", "question_tokens": ["Even", "if", "it", "works", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 325, "answer": "Oh, especially if it works.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "especially", "if", "it", "works", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 331, "question": "How many of them do you believe were justified?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "of", "them", "do", "you", "believe", "were", "justified", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "Well, justified plus legal --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "justified", "plus", "legal", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "But how many of the major conflicts have been legitimate?", "question_tokens": ["But", "how", "many", "of", "the", "major", "conflicts", "have", "been", "legitimate", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "Well, from a constitutional viewpoint I don't want to fight any wars that aren't declared.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "from", "a", "constitutional", "viewpoint", "I", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "fight", "any", "wars", "that", "are", "n't", "declared", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "Do you support the conflict in Afghanistan?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "support", "the", "conflict", "in", "Afghanistan", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "I did, but that's to go after only those responsible for 9/11.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", ",", "but", "that", "'s", "to", "go", "after", "only", "those", "responsible", "for", "9/11", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Afghanistan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Qaeda"]}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 345, "question": "But it was war, wasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["But", "it", "was", "war", ",", "was", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "To go after al Qaeda, it was like going after criminals.", "answer_tokens": ["To", "go", "after", "al", "Qaeda", ",", "it", "was", "like", "going", "after", "criminals", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "Was it constitutional?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "constitutional", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "Yes, to a degree because it was limited.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "to", "a", "degree", "because", "it", "was", "limited", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "Wouldn't they?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "There is no evidence to that.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "is", "no", "evidence", "to", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "If Iran was to strike back at Israel, what would you do?", "question_tokens": ["If", "Iran", "was", "to", "strike", "back", "at", "Israel", ",", "what", "would", "you", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "Well, I go and look to the rules.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "go", "and", "look", "to", "the", "rules", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iran", "Israel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CIA"], "LOCATION": ["Mossad"]}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "CD", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VB", "VBZ", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 377, "question": "If you believe Iran had enough enriched uranium to genuinely launch a nuclear attack against Israel, would that knowledge alone mean you would countenance military action?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "believe", "Iran", "had", "enough", "enriched", "uranium", "to", "genuinely", "launch", "a", "nuclear", "attack", "against", "Israel", ",", "would", "that", "knowledge", "alone", "mean", "you", "would", "countenance", "military", "action", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "MD", "IN", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 378, "answer": "Well, the one thing that we should set aside is there's our CIA and the Mossad.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "one", "thing", "that", "we", "should", "set", "aside", "is", "there", "'s", "our", "CIA", "and", "the", "Mossad", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iran", "Israel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "You wouldn't ever countenance any preemptive strike?", "question_tokens": ["You", "would", "n't", "ever", "countenance", "any", "preemptive", "strike", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "No, not really.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "really", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "JJ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "If you were president of the Second World War, and you had been given knowledge the Japanese were planning Pearl Harbor, you would have preemptively struck, wouldn't you?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "were", "president", "of", "the", "Second", "World", "War", ",", "and", "you", "had", "been", "given", "knowledge", "the", "Japanese", "were", "planning", "Pearl", "Harbor", ",", "you", "would", "have", "preemptively", "struck", ",", "would", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "VBD", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VB", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "Well, let me touch your first subject first.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "let", "me", "touch", "your", "first", "subject", "first", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Pearl Harbor"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "You're not seriously defending Ahmadinejad, are you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "not", "seriously", "defending", "Ahmadinejad", ",", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "I'm trying to defend honesty.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "trying", "to", "defend", "honesty", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", ",", "RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "I come back to that question I put to you: if you had knowledge and you were president when Pearl Harbor happened, if you had pre-knowledge of that happening, would you have attacked?", "question_tokens": ["I", "come", "back", "to", "that", "question", "I", "put", "to", "you", ":", "if", "you", "had", "knowledge", "and", "you", "were", "president", "when", "Pearl", "Harbor", "happened", ",", "if", "you", "had", "pre-knowledge", "of", "that", "happening", ",", "would", "you", "have", "attacked", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBG", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "Imminent attack -- if we're sitting here and we see the planes come over, obviously, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Imminent", "attack", "--", "if", "we", "'re", "sitting", "here", "and", "we", "see", "the", "planes", "come", "over", ",", "obviously", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Pearl Harbor"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel"]}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", ",", "VB", "NN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "Because I think that they would, if they could, consider attacking Israel.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "think", "that", "they", "would", ",", "if", "they", "could", ",", "consider", "attacking", "Israel", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "But aren't there times when you have to be the policeman of the world?", "question_tokens": ["But", "are", "n't", "there", "times", "when", "you", "have", "to", "be", "the", "policeman", "of", "the", "world", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 437, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 438, "answer": "It is not.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "What's your honest opinion about gay marriage?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "honest", "opinion", "about", "gay", "marriage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "I -- I am totally neutral on the cause of liberty when people want to be married and call it a marriage, it's none of my business.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "I", "am", "totally", "neutral", "on", "the", "cause", "of", "liberty", "when", "people", "want", "to", "be", "married", "and", "call", "it", "a", "marriage", ",", "it", "'s", "none", "of", "my", "business", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 466, "question": "But you witnessed this?", "question_tokens": ["But", "you", "witnessed", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 467, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "I walked out of the room and thought, wow, what did I just see?", "question_tokens": ["I", "walked", "out", "of", "the", "room", "and", "thought", ",", "wow", ",", "what", "did", "I", "just", "see", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", ",", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "But that clearly scarred you.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "that", "clearly", "scarred", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 480, "question": "But if they were, would you honestly look at them in the eye and say they had to have that child if they were impregnated?", "question_tokens": ["But", "if", "they", "were", ",", "would", "you", "honestly", "look", "at", "them", "in", "the", "eye", "and", "say", "they", "had", "to", "have", "that", "child", "if", "they", "were", "impregnated", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 481, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "You would allow them to abort the baby?", "question_tokens": ["You", "would", "allow", "them", "to", "abort", "the", "baby", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "It is absolutely in limbo, because an hour after intercourse or a day afterwards, there is no legal or medical problem.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "absolutely", "in", "limbo", ",", "because", "an", "hour", "after", "intercourse", "or", "a", "day", "afterwards", ",", "there", "is", "no", "legal", "or", "medical", "problem", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 488, "question": "Life doesn't begin at conception?", "question_tokens": ["Life", "does", "n't", "begin", "at", "conception", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "Life does begin at conception.", "answer_tokens": ["Life", "does", "begin", "at", "conception", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 521, "question": "Finally on this point, do you accept there is a slight contradiction between a candidate who is pro liberty, pro personal choice, pro personal responsibility in almost every other area, but on the specific area says no, you don't have choice?", "question_tokens": ["Finally", "on", "this", "point", ",", "do", "you", "accept", "there", "is", "a", "slight", "contradiction", "between", "a", "candidate", "who", "is", "pro", "liberty", ",", "pro", "personal", "choice", ",", "pro", "personal", "responsibility", "in", "almost", "every", "other", "area", ",", "but", "on", "the", "specific", "area", "says", "no", ",", "you", "do", "n't", "have", "choice", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBP", "NN", ",", "NN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "See, I don't see the inconsistency because I see the nine- pound baby that's still within the mother as deserving some protection, too.", "answer_tokens": ["See", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "see", "the", "inconsistency", "because", "I", "see", "the", "nine-", "pound", "baby", "that", "'s", "still", "within", "the", "mother", "as", "deserving", "some", "protection", ",", "too", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "How many grandchildren?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "grandchildren", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "Eighteen.", "answer_tokens": ["Eighteen", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "How many great grandchildren?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "great", "grandchildren", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "Five.", "answer_tokens": ["Five", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 558, "question": "What's the secret to a long lasting marriage, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "secret", "to", "a", "long", "lasting", "marriage", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 559, "answer": "I think a lot is respect and acceptance of both of our shortcomings.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "a", "lot", "is", "respect", "and", "acceptance", "of", "both", "of", "our", "shortcomings", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 565, "question": "If Carol was here, what would she say your shortcomings are?", "question_tokens": ["If", "Carol", "was", "here", ",", "what", "would", "she", "say", "your", "shortcomings", "are", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 566, "answer": "She'd probably be pretty generous, you know.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "'d", "probably", "be", "pretty", "generous", ",", "you", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Carol"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 568, "question": "If you were being self- critical?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "were", "being", "self-", "critical", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 569, "answer": "Well, I can get upset.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "can", "get", "upset", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 578, "question": "Were you a spanker when you were young?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "a", "spanker", "when", "you", "were", "young", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 579, "answer": "No, not really.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "really", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", ",", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "Do you believe parents should still have that right to give their kids a little tap?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "parents", "should", "still", "have", "that", "right", "to", "give", "their", "kids", "a", "little", "tap", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "Oh, yeah, as long as they're not practicing severe child abuse.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yeah", ",", "as", "long", "as", "they", "'re", "not", "practicing", "severe", "child", "abuse", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 595, "question": "We discussed hard work, but what else?", "question_tokens": ["We", "discussed", "hard", "work", ",", "but", "what", "else", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "NN", ",", "CC", "WP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 596, "answer": "I think it's hard work.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "hard", "work", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 608, "question": "Or do you think that's what the American dream, at its purest, is about?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "do", "you", "think", "that", "'s", "what", "the", "American", "dream", ",", "at", "its", "purest", ",", "is", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "POS", "WP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 609, "answer": "I think it is.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 618, "question": "Giants or Patriots, Super Bowl?", "question_tokens": ["Giants", "or", "Patriots", ",", "Super", "Bowl", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "CC", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 619, "answer": "Super Bowl, haven't paid much attention to it.", "answer_tokens": ["Super", "Bowl", ",", "have", "n't", "paid", "much", "attention", "to", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 624, "question": "How important is it that you perform well in Nevada?", "question_tokens": ["How", "important", "is", "it", "that", "you", "perform", "well", "in", "Nevada", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 625, "answer": "I think it's very important.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "very", "important", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Nevada"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 635, "question": "ORGAN: But Nothing will stop you before the convention?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "But", "Nothing", "will", "stop", "you", "before", "the", "convention", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "CC", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 636, "answer": "I'm not thinking in those terms because I'm thinking in campaigning where the next stop is.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "thinking", "in", "those", "terms", "because", "I", "'m", "thinking", "in", "campaigning", "where", "the", "next", "stop", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 641, "question": "Or are you implacably opposed to doing that just on principle?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "are", "you", "implacably", "opposed", "to", "doing", "that", "just", "on", "principle", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "NN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 642, "answer": "Well, it would be a real challenge, but I think people change their minds.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "would", "be", "a", "real", "challenge", ",", "but", "I", "think", "people", "change", "their", "minds", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 663, "question": "What does it feel like to start with one person and then slowly start to build the organization?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "it", "feel", "like", "to", "start", "with", "one", "person", "and", "then", "slowly", "start", "to", "build", "the", "organization", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CD", "NN", "CC", "RB", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 664, "answer": "I found that if you have a good idea and you do it with love, a lot of people want to help you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "found", "that", "if", "you", "have", "a", "good", "idea", "and", "you", "do", "it", "with", "love", ",", "a", "lot", "of", "people", "want", "to", "help", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Christine"]}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 669, "question": "What was your sister's name?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "sister", "'s", "name", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 670, "answer": "IM: Her name is Christine.", "answer_tokens": ["IM", ":", "Her", "name", "is", "Christine", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Achei"]}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "CD", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 674, "question": "What kind of an impact do you think this will have?", "question_tokens": ["What", "kind", "of", "an", "impact", "do", "you", "think", "this", "will", "have", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 675, "answer": "The clinic we have in Achei, in the tsunami zone, that one is really safe.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "clinic", "we", "have", "in", "Achei", ",", "in", "the", "tsunami", "zone", ",", "that", "one", "is", "really", "safe", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 688, "question": "I mean, in those dark days when -- when you don't have money and when you don't have support?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "in", "those", "dark", "days", "when", "--", "when", "you", "do", "n't", "have", "money", "and", "when", "you", "do", "n't", "have", "support", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WRB", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 689, "answer": "Some days I don't have money, but I always have support.", "answer_tokens": ["Some", "days", "I", "do", "n't", "have", "money", ",", "but", "I", "always", "have", "support", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Buffalo"]}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 713, "question": "Giants or Patriots, Wolf?", "question_tokens": ["Giants", "or", "Patriots", ",", "Wolf", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "CC", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 714, "answer": "I'm a Buffalo Bills fan.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "a", "Buffalo", "Bills", "fan", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Wolf"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John King"]}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 716, "question": "Gloria?", "question_tokens": ["Gloria", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 717, "answer": "All right, I'm standing next to John King, OK, so I have to say the Patriots.", "answer_tokens": ["All", "right", ",", "I", "'m", "standing", "next", "to", "John", "King", ",", "OK", ",", "so", "I", "have", "to", "say", "the", "Patriots", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 719, "question": "Giants or Patriots?", "question_tokens": ["Giants", "or", "Patriots", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "CC", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 720, "answer": "Neither.", "answer_tokens": ["Neither", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]